<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<email>
  <receiver>multipledogsatonce@gmail.com</receiver>
  <sender>Dracula Daily draculadaily@substack.com</sender>
  <content>
    View this post on the web at https://draculadaily.substack.com/p/dracula-oc=
    tober-31-506

    Jonathan Harker's Journal.
    31 October.=E2=80=94Still hurrying along. The day has come, and Godalming i=
    s sleeping. I am on watch. The morning is bitterly cold; the furnace heat i=
    s grateful, though we have heavy fur coats. As yet we have passed only a fe=
    w open boats, but none of them had on board any box or package of anything =
    like the size of the one we seek. The men were scared every time we turned =
    our electric lamp on them, and fell on their knees and prayed.
    Mina Harker's Journal.
    31 October.=E2=80=94Arrived at Veresti at noon. The Professor tells me that=
    his morning at dawn he could hardly hypnotise me at all, and that all I c=
    ould say was: "dark and quiet." He is off now buying a carriage and horses.=
    He says that he will later on try to buy additional horses, so that we may=
    be able to change them on the way. We have something more than 70 miles be=
    fore us. The country is lovely, and most interesting; if only we were under=
    different conditions, how delightful it would be to see it all. If Jonatha=
    n and I were driving through it alone what a pleasure it would be. To stop =
    and see people, and learn something of their life, and to fill our minds an=
    d memories with all the colour and picturesqueness of the whole wild, beaut=
    iful country and the quaint people! But, alas!=E2=80=94
    Later.=E2=80=94Dr. Van Helsing has returned. He has got the carriage and ho=
    rses; we are to have some dinner, and to start in an hour. The landlady is =
    putting us up a huge basket of provisions; it seems enough for a company of=
    soldiers. The Professor encourages her, and whispers to me that it may be =
    a week before we can get any good food again. He has been shopping too, and=
    has sent home such a wonderful lot of fur coats and wraps, and all sorts o=
    f warm things. There will not be any chance of our being cold.
    We shall soon be off. I am afraid to think what may happen to us. We are tr=
    uly in the hands of God. He alone knows what may be, and I pray Him, with a=
    ll the strength of my sad and humble soul, that He will watch over my belov=
    ed husband; that whatever may happen, Jonathan may know that I loved him an=
    d honoured him more than I can say, and that my latest and truest thought w=
    ill be always for him.

    Unsubscribe https://substack.com/redirect/2/eyJlIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly9kcmFjdWxhZGF=
    pbHkuc3Vic3RhY2suY29tL2FjdGlvbi9kaXNhYmxlX2VtYWlsP3Rva2VuPWV5SjFjMlZ5WDJsa0=
    lqbzVNVEl6TnpJMk1Dd2ljRzl6ZEY5cFpDSTZNVFE0TWpRMk5EQXhMQ0pwWVhRaU9qRTNNekF6T=
    npZMk9USXNJbVY0Y0NJNk1UYzJNVGt4TWpZNU1pd2lhWE56SWpvaWNIVmlMVEkxTXpNME1TSXNJ=
    bk4xWWlJNkltUnBjMkZpYkdWZlpXMWhhV3dpZlEuSVdHS3NPUFhoZUtCcjFLYlQxUVM5VWxXUlp=
    sck5BVDhfWGF3RUppUzc1byIsInAiOjE0ODI0NjQwMSwicyI6MjUzMzQxLCJmIjp0cnVlLCJ1Ij=
    o5MTIzNzI2MCwiaWF0IjoxNzMwMzc2NjkyLCJleHAiOjE3MzI5Njg2OTIsImlzcyI6InB1Yi0wI=
    iwic3ViIjoibGluay1yZWRpcmVjdCJ9.h6UwHmNh4yHziXQqzx_-rkPpgsO3k9Irciu-6zlRCEg=
    ?
  </content>
</email>  